Executive Producer
Kadokawa Tsuguhiko
Producers
Inoue Shinichiro
Egawa Shinya
Kawashima Haruo
Kawasaki Shiroharu
Morimoto Yoshihisa
Sakaki Shunto
Production
Maruta Jungo
Based on the novel by
Yasutaka Tsutsui
The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Today, July 13th, is known as NICE day.
What does that mean?
Producers
Saito Yuichiro
Watanabe Takashi
General Production
Yasuda Takeshi
Planning
Maruyama Masao
From 7(NAna)-1(Ichi)-3(San), you get NICE(na-i-su).
Screenplay
Okudera Satoko
Music
Yoshida Shigeru
Theme Song
Oku Hanako
Photography
Tomita Yoshihiro
Sound Director
Ohara Yoshio
Editor
Nishiyama Shigeru
Computer Graphics
Hayashi Hiromi
Color Coordinator
Kamata Chikako
Art Director
Yamamoto Fumi
Character Designer
Sadamoto Yoshiyuki
Animation Directors
Aoyama Hiroyuki
Kubota Chikai
Ishihama Shinji
Director
Hosoda Mamoru
Tempura
Try harder
Tuesday, July 12th.
Today, Japanese Standard Time...
So, why is today, July 13th, known as NICE day?
Today something really great happened!
What should I do?
What, what happened? Tell me!
Looks like I got confessed
to. Aren't you jealous?
A Picture of White Plum, Two Camellia and Chrysanthemum.
Currently in restoration.
Walking home and fooling around
I was teasing you for no reason
I wanted to see different faces of you
With big eyes and voice about to cry
Even now it squeezes my heart
I was chasing you in a crowd of strangers
I was looking for unchanging things
I won't forget you of that day
Some thoughts can cross the time
I want to see you right now
The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Your back, running on the playground
was freer than the clouds floating in the sky
and even the square letters in my notebook
all were as if illuminated by the light
I didn't know what love means
but that time that will never return
explained to me the meaning of it
I will store the days I spent with you in my heart
so that I won't have to remember them
Even if one day I'll fall in love with someone else
you will be always special and dear to me
This season will come around again
Meeting you inside the endless time
more than anything, made me stronger
Even if I reach the tomorrow of the dream
you will be always special and dear to me
This season will arrive again
In the summer when you said "I will never forget you"
the time has flown and now I've shed my tears
I will store the days I spent with you in my heart
so that I won't have to remember them
Even if one day I'll fall in love with someone else
you will be always special and dear to me
This season will come around again